https://learningservices.com/privacy-policy/

Learning Services and ReMed have merged to form one great continuum of care
Privacy Policy
Learning Services Corporation respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it. Learning Services provides this Internet Privacy Statement to inform you of our Privacy Policy and practices used on learningservices.com.
Information Collection and Use
Learning Services is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways other than those outlined in this statement. Learning Services collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site. Personal info provided by users will be used by the LS to improve the site and provide a more personalized experience for the user, but information which identifies a specific individual will not be disclosed to others without the user’s permission unless necessary to provide services which the user has requested.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes the browser, the cookie simply terminates. If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users as they visit different sections of our site.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movement, and gather broad information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Sharing
We will share aggregate information with our partners and advertisers. This aggregate information does not contain personally identifiable information and therefore cannot identify any specific individual. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
Links
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Learning Services is not responsible for the privacy practices of such sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. The Learning Services privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the Learning Services Web site.
Security
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. All of our users’ information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. The servers used to store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. If you have any questions about the security at our Web site, you can use our contact form.
Supplementation of Information
In order for this Web site to enhance its ability to tailor the site to an individual’s preference, we might combine information about the purchasing habits of users with similar information from other partners, to create a personalized user profile. The personalized user profile will be used to improve the site and provide a more personalized experience for the user, but will not be disclosed to others.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post changes on our Privacy Policy page so our users are always aware of the information we collect, the ways we use it, and any circumstances under which we disclose it.
To make a referral, please call:1.888.419.9955
Copyright © 2020 Learning Services Corp.
